Guide to the Jack Anderson papers, 1930-2004 MS2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual, 1990 March 14; 1969-2001; MS2001 Series 11; 3.5 Linear Feet 3 videocassette boxes, 1 document box
  - Jack Anderson Presents the Freedom Package [2 of 2] [folder of audiocassettes], Undated; Series 11 (Box 450, Folder 2)
- Personal, Undated; 1938-2000; MS2001 Series 12; 4 Linear Feet 6 document boxes, 1 flat box
  This series contains records that document Anderson's education, early journalistic work, military service, LDS mission, and family life. It includes correspondence, newspaper articles, notes, and military service manuals. These materials date from 1930 (a Story of the Three Bears book given to Anderson as a child) to 2000.
  Anderson came to his calling early, and his early journalistic work includes articles he wrote for local newspapers as an adolescent. At 12 years old, he began writing the Boy Scout column for local newspaper The Deseret News, and soon graduated to covering local news for The Murray Eagle newspaper. In high school, he edited the school newspaper The Granitian while serving as president of his class.
  Anderson briefly enrolled at the University of Utah until, as a practicing member of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints, he undertook a mission through the American south in 1941. Records from the mission are included in this series.
  Upon his return, he volunteered for the Merchant Marine, first serving as a war correspondent in occupied China until 1945, when he was inducted into the Army, and then serving in the Quartermaster Corps and writing for Stars and Stripes newspaper. Anderson's military manuals, documents, and copies of an Anderson article in the Stars and Stripes newspaper are also included in this series.
  - Academic notes [1 of 2], 1938-1940; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Academic notes [2 of 2], Undated; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Author and Journalist magazine, 1938; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scout articles by Anderson - Deseret News, 1939-1941; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Do Your Own Printing magazine, Undated; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 5)
  - Draft articles and notes, Undated; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 6)
  - Granite High School, Undated; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 7)
  - LDS church [1 of 6], Undated; Series 12 (Box 393, Folder 8)
  - LDS church [2 of 6], Undated; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - LDS church [3 of 6], Undated; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - LDS church [4 of 6], Undated; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - LDS church [5 of 6], 1932-1942; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 4)
  - LDS church [6 of 6], Undated; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 5)
  - LDS mission and early experiences, Undated; Series 12 (Box 394, Folder 6)
  - Military service, Undated; Series 12 (Box 395, Folder 1)
  - Military service - manuals [1 of 2], 1944; Series 12 (Box 395, Folder 2)
  - Military service - manuals [2 of 2], 1944; Series 12 (Box 395, Folder 3)
  - Military service - Sea Project [1 of 3], 1944; Series 12 (Box 395, Folder 4)
  - Military service - Sea Project [2 of 3], Undated; Series 12 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - Military service - Sea Project [3 of 3], 1936; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - Religious Research Association, 1930; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 2)
  - Scout newspaper, Undated; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 3)
  - Story of the Three Bears, 1940; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 4)
  - Strictly Personal: Excerpts from my Diary, 1940; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 5)
  - University of Utah, 1938-1940; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 6)
  - University of Utah - notes, 1939; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 7)
  - Writer's Digest, undated; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 8)
  - Writer's Yearbook, undated; Series 12 (Box 396, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Merchant Marine Cadet School [1 of 2], undated; Series 12 (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Merchant Marine Cadet School [2 of 2], 1937-1940; Series 12 (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - Personal -- general, 1946; Series 12 (Box 443, Folder 4)
  - Articles by and about Anderson, 1946; Series 12 (Box 456, Folder 3)
  - Stars and Stripes China Edition, 1937-1938; Series 12 (Box 456, Folder 4)
  - Stars and Stripes China Edition -- Anderson byline, 1939; Series 12 (Box 456, Folder 5)
  - Granitian [high school newspaper of which Anderson was editor], 1964-2006; Series 12 (Box 456, Folder 6)
  - Murray Eagle [newspaper for which Anderson wrote in his youth], 1996; Series 12 (Box 456, Folder 7)
- Artifacts, 1992; 1964-2006; MS2001 Series 13; 25 Linear Feet 19 document boxes, 13 flat boxes, 1 record center box, 1 object
  They are not arranged but merely grouped according to size and shape as necessary for storage.
  This series consists primarily of awards presented to Anderson by organizations, clubs, and municipalities. Most awards are either plaques or paperweights of some type, and all are engraved with the name and date of the award. They date from 1958 to 2006. The series also includes Anderson's white Olympia typewriter.
  - Award, The One Hundred Club of Buffalo and Western New York, undated; Series 13 (Box 406, Object 1)
  - Award, Boypower Dinner, Twin Rivers Council [Boy Scouts], undated; Series 13 (Box 406, Object 2)
  - Award, Iowa Newspaper Foundation, undated; Series 13 (Box 406, Object 3)
  - Award, American Society of Criminology, undated; Series 13 (Box 406, Object 4)
  - "Wagon Boss" badge award, Colorado Press Association, 1992; Series 13 (Box 406, Object 5)
  - "Man for All Seasons" award, International Platform Association (glass fragile), undated; Series 13 (Box 407, Object 1)
  - Freedom Magazine Human Rights Leadership Award, 1966; Series 13 (Box 407, Object 2)
  - Award, Wayne State University, undated; Series 13 (Box 407, Object 3)
  - Award, Department of Journalism and Public Relations, American University, 1981; Series 13 (Box 407, Object 4)
  - Medal, Presidential Protective Force, Korea (with business card), 1970; Series 13 (Box 407, Object 5)
  - Award, Chicago Area Council, Boy Scouts of America, Mercantile Industry Lunch-o-ree, undated; Series 13 (Box 408, Object 1)
  - "Granny Award," Most Famous '40 Grad, Class of '40 reunion, 1988; Series 13 (Box 408, Object 2)
  - Award, with the compliments of Min, Kwan-Shik, Vice Speaker, National Assembly, Republic of Korea, 1995; Series 13 (Box 408, Object 3)
  - Award, Distinguished Speakers Program, U.S. Air Force Academy, 1994; Series 13 (Box 408, Object 4)
  - Award, Dinamation International Corp., 1974; Series 13 (Box 408, Object 5)
  - Award, Young Astronauts of Korea, 7th Young Astronauts Conference, 1989; Series 13 (Box 409, Object 1)
  - Mug, "Jack Anderson, Fall Guy, Baltimore, 1974", 1983; Series 13 (Box 409, Object 2)
  - Award with clock, WCBC 12th Annual Community Achievement Awards, undated; Series 13 (Box 409, Object 3)
  - Award, The Michael Jackson Program, KABC Talkradio, Undated; Series 13 (Box 409, Object 4)
  - Plaque (reproduction of book jacket), "McCarthy: The Man, the Senator, the 'Ism'", 1988; Series 13 (Box 410, Object 1)
  - Plaque (reproduction of book jacket), "USA: Second Class Power?", 1971; Series 13 (Box 410, Object 2)
  - Award, Caterama 1988, Boston, Massachusetts, 1975; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 1)
  - Award (key), Philadelphia Public Relations Association, 1966; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 2)
  - Award, The Press Club of San Francisco, 1972; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 3)
  - Associated In-Group Donors award, Annual Luncheon, undated; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 4)
  - Plaque, New York Times article, 1/6/1972, 1994; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 5)
  - Award, National Communications Advisory Board, Brigham Young University, 1988-1989; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 6)
  - Department of Communications, undated; Series 13 (Box 411, Object 7)
  - "WeTIP" award, On Behalf of Concerned Parents Everywhere, 1984; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 1)
  - "John F. Kennedy Astronautics Award," American Astronautical Society, 1982; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 2)
  - Award, National Association of Postmasters of the United States, 1978; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 3)
  - Award, Process Equipment Manufacturers Association, Warren Woods Memorial Scholarship, 1965; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 4)
  - Award, U.S. Customs Service, 1964; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 5)
  - "National School Bell Award", 1980; Series 13 (Box 412, Object 6)
  - Award, B'Nai B'Rith of Washington, DC, 1999; Series 13 (Box 413, Object 1)
  - Award, "National Speakers Night," Sales and Marketing Executives of Erie, 1972; Series 13 (Box 413, Object 2)
  - Award, National Council for Youth Health Reform, 1990; Series 13 (Box 413, Object 3)
  - Honorary Commodore award, Stockton Chamber of Commerce, undated; Series 13 (Box 413, Object 4)
  - Award, Public Transit Expo '90, 1986; Series 13 (Box 413, Object 5)
  - Award, Toastmasters International, Virginia Cavaliers, undated; Series 13 (Box 414, Object 1)
  - Award, Future Farmers of America, 1972; Series 13 (Box 414, Object 2)
  - Plaque (reproduction of book jacket), "USA: Second Class Power?", 1986; Series 13 (Box 414, Object 3)
  - Meritorious Citation, Affiliated Young Democrats, Inc., New York state, 1988; Series 13 (Box 416, Object 1)
  - Blue and Gold Award, Future Farmers of America, 1973; Series 13 (Box 416, Object 2)
  - Award, The Adcraft Club of Detroit, 1994; Series 13 (Box 415, Object 1)
  - Brass award plate, Circus Saints and Sinners Club, undated; Series 13 (Box 415, Object 2)
  - Brass award plate, NOWL Journalistic Achievement Award, 1972; Series 13 (Box 415, Object 3)
  - Engraved name plate, 1974; Series 13 (Box 415, Object 4)
  - Award, Kappa Tau Alpha, James Melvin Lee Chapter, New York University, 1975; Series 13 (Box 415, Object 5)
  - Plaque, World Taekwondo Federation, undated; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 1)
  - "John Marshall Law School Freedom Award", 1969-1986; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 2)
  - Engraved pen holder, 2006; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 3)
  - Meeting badges, undated; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 4)
  - Framed Herblock cartoon, "Jack Northman Anderson: Pogo's Good Government Hall of Fame,", undated; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 5)
  - NASA patch, 1971; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 6)
  - "Free Les Whitten" button, undated; Series 13 (Box 417, Object 7)
  - Award, The One Hundred Club of Buffalo, 1986; Series 13 (Box 418, Object 1)
  - "Alice in Blunderland" book poster, undated; Series 13 (Box 418, Object 2)
  - Award, "Print New Jersey, Inc.", undated; Series 13 (Box 418, Object 3)
  - Paper award certificates and oversized posters, 1995; Series 13 (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Stained glass replica of Anderson's desk [FRAGILE], 1983; Series 13 (Box 419, Object 1)
  - Shining Star Award, Moose International, 1974; Series 13 (Box 420, Object 1)
  - Golden Plate, American Academy of Achievement, 1983; Series 13 (Box 421, Object 1)
  - National Commander's Public Relations Award, American Legion, 1991; Series 13 (Box 421, Object 2)
  - Eagle trophy, Peterson Award for Excellence in Journalism, National Association for Home Care, 1978; Series 13 (Box 422, Object 1)
  - Award, Economics Club of Orlando, 1987; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 1)
  - Award, American Oceanic Association, for excellent in investigative reporting, 1982; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 2)
  - Award, Charter Member of the Board of Directors, Treedom Foundation, 1988; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 3)
  - Bookplate, Brandeis University, 1988; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 4)
  - Award, UASCD Conference, undated; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 5)
  - Award, Outstanding Contribution to the Young Astronaut Program, 1982; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 6)
  - Accolade for Professionalism in Communications, Advertising/Communications Times, 1982; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 7)
  - Award, Chicago Area Council, Boy Scouts of America, 1975; Series 13 (Box 423, Object 8)
  - Award, KSEN Radio, Cut Bank, Montana, 1988; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 1)
  - Award, 1st World Black Belt League Team Championships, 1985; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 2)
  - Award, National Head Start Association, 1982; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 3)
  - Award, Compensation Management, 1981; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 4)
  - Award, Wife Forum for Famous Americans, 1958; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 5)
  - Award, Asian Safari Club, undated; Series 13 (Box 424, Object 6)
  - Award, Poor Richard Club of Philadelphia, 1969; Series 13 (Box 273, Object 1)
  - Key to the City of Flint, MI, undated; Series 13 (Box 273, Object 2)
  - Award, Southwest Journalism Forum, undated; Series 13 (Box 273, Object 3)
  - Key to the City of Atlantic City, undated; Series 13 (Box 273, Object 4)
  - Gift, President of the Phillipines, undated; Series 13 (Box 273, Object 5)
  - Anderson's typewriter, undated; Series 13 (Object 1)
  - Buttons and patches, 2009; Series 13 (Box 456, Folder 1)
- Anderson FBI Files Obtained by National Security Archive, 2009; MS2001 Series 14; 1.5 Linear Feet 3 document boxes
  This series consists of FBI files on Jack Anderson that were donated to Gelman Library's Special Collections Research Center by the National Security Archive. The NSA compiled them from two separate sources: first, from papers received as a result of Michael Ravnitsky's FOIA request on Jack Anderson. (Ravnitsky has made a project of filing requests on certain people and then donating the documents to the NSA); and second, from papers that the NSA received after filing its own FOIA request on Anderson in 2005.
  Arranged as found.
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [1 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Cd 1)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [2 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Folder 2)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [3 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [4 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Folder 4)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [5 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [6 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 451, Folder 6)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [7 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [8 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 452, Folder 2)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [9 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 452, Folder 3)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [10 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [11 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 452, Folder 5)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [12 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 1)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [13 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [14 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [15 of 17], 2009; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 4)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [16 of 17], 1941-1992; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - Anderson FBI files obtained by the National Security Archive [17 of 17], Undated; Series 14 (Box 453, Folder 6)
- Daryl Gibson research files from Peace, War, and Politics, 1941-1944; Series 15; 2.5 Linear Feet
  Subseries 1 of the Daryl Gibson research files are open for research.
  Subseries 2, containing audio materials, is closed to the public until 2020.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials gathered by Daryl Gibson while researching for Anderson's 1999 autobiography Peace, War, and Politics: An Eyewitness Account, for which she served as co-author.
  Materials include copies of key documents and articles, as well as audio interviews with Anderson and colleagues. Paper files include copies of materials from 1941-1991, and audio recordings include interviews conducted by Daryl Gibson with Anderson and his colleagues between 1993 and 1998.
  Arrangement
  Paper files are arranged alphabetically, and audio files are arranged chronologically.
  - Paper files, 1945-1946; Series 15 Subseries 1; 2 Linear Feet
    Materials include copies of key documents and articles from Anderson's career, from 1941-1991.
    - Anderson early years -- education, Merchant Marine, undated; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - Anderson's passport, 1971-1991; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 2)
    - Anderson photographs, 1973; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 3)
    - Articles about Anderson, 1972-1992; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs -- Les Whitten arrest, 1977-1980; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 5)
    - Business deals, undated; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Jimmy, undated; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 7)
    - Cartoons featuring Anderson, 1975-1989; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 8)
    - China / Chou-en-Lai and Jack's military career, 1976-1977; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1966; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 9)
    - Diplomat Bank, 1972; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 10)
    - Dodd, Thomas, 1961; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 11)
    - Eagleton, Thomas, 1959-1962; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 12)
    - Eichmann, Adolf, undated; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 13)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1975; Series 15 (Box 460, Folder 14)
    - FBI file, undated; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 5)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1958; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - Gaddafi, Muammar, 1973; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 2)
    - Goldfine and Adams, undated; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 3)
    - Gray, Patrick, undated; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1968; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1975; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 1)
    - Howard Hughes/Robert Mayheu, undated; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 6)
    - Hume, Brit, 1980; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 7)
    - India/Pakistan, 1970-1973; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 2)
    - Iran -- Dale Van Atta, undated; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 8)
    - ITT, undated; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1954; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 10)
    - Kennedy, John F. and Kennedy, Robert, 1970; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Ted, 1975; Series 15 (Box 461, Folder 11)
    - Laxalt, Paul, 1962-1966; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 1)
    - Liddy, G. Gordon, undated; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 2)
    - Mafia, 1977-1978; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - Mitchell, Martha, 1977-1978; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Nixon, Richard [1 of 2], 1975; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, Richard [2 of 2], 1975; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - Oil, 1947-1974; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 7)
    - Onassis, Aristotle, 1941; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 8)
    - Pearson, Drew, undated; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 9)
    - Polygamy, undated; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 10)
    - Project Mudhen [1 of 2], undated; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 11)
    - Project Mudhen [2 of 2], 1982-1983; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 12)
    - Project Mudhen, 1972-1984; Series 15 (Box R14, Folder 4)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1962-1974; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 13)
    - Style, ethics, and techniques, 1978-1981; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Presidents, 1978-1981; Series 15 (Box 462, Folder 15)
    - Vesco, Robert [1 of 2], 1972-1973; Series 15 (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Vesco, Robert [2 of 2], Undated; Series 15 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Watergate, 1983; Series 15 (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - Audio materials -- closed until 2020, 1993 October 7; Series 15 Subseries 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains recordings of interviews between Daryl Gibson and Jack Anderson, Dale Van Atta, Les Whitten, Joe Spear, and Mike Binstein during the course of Gibson's research for Anderson's 1999 autobiography Peace, War, and Politics: An Eyewitness Account, for which she served as co-author. The interviews were conducted between 1992 and 1998.
    - Freedom Festival Fireside - Jack Anderson, 1993 October 7; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 1)
    - Interview #1: Jack Anderson - Early Years, 1993 October 12; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 2)
    - Interview #2: Jack Anderson - Early Years, 1993 November 11; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 3)
    - Interview #3: Jack Anderson - Pearson Years, 1993 November 11; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 4)
    - Interview #4: Jack Anderson - Pearson Years, 1993 November 11; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 5)
    - Interview #5: Jack Anderson - Pearson Years, 1993 December 1; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 6)
    - Interview #6: Jack Anderson - Pearson Years, 1993 December 1; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 7)
    - Interview #7: Jack Anderson - Pearson Years, 1993 December 4; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 8)
    - Interview #8: Jack Anderson, 1994 January 10; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 9)
    - Interview #9: Jack Anderson - Chappoquidick and Hoover, 1994 January 1; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 10)
    - Interview #10: Jack Anderson, 1994 January 11, 13; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 11)
    - Interview #11: Jack Anderson, 1994 January 13, 29; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 12)
    - Interview #12: Jack Anderson, 1994 January 29; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 13)
    - Interview #13: Jack Anderson, 1994 January 29 - 1994 February 21; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 14)
    - Interview #14: Jack Anderson, 1994 February 21; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 15)
    - Interview #15: Jack Anderson, 1994 February 21 - March 21; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 16)
    - Interview #16: Jack Anderson, 1994 March 21; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 17)
    - Interview #17: Jack Anderson, 1994 October 6; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 18)
    - Interview #18: Jack Anderson, 1994 October 12; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 19)
    - Interview #19: Jack Anderson, 1994 October 12; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 20)
    - Interview #20: Jack Anderson, 1992 June 11; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 21)
    - Interview #21: Jack Anderson, 1992 June 12; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 22)
    - Interview #22: Jack Anderson - JFK Assassination, 1994 June 25; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 23)
    - Interview #23: Jack Anderson - JFK, 1994 June 25; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 24)
    - Interview #1: Dale Van Atta, 1994 June 25; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 25)
    - Interview #2: Dale Van Atta, 1994 June 25; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 26)
    - Interview #3: Dale Van Atta, 1994 September 30; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 26)
    - Interview #4: Dale Van Atta, 1994 September 30; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 27)
    - Interview #1: Les Whitten, 1994 October 17; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 28)
    - Interview #2: Les Whitten, 1994 October 17; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 29)
    - Interview #1: Joe Spear, 1994 October 17; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 30)
    - Interview #2: Joe Spear, 1994 December 3; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 31)
    - Interview #3: Joe Spear, 1994 December 3; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 32)
    - Interview #1: Mike Binstein, 1998 January 10; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 33)
    - Interview #2: Mike Binstein, 1998 January 10; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 34)
    - Interview: "Original - Tape #1 Nancy Murphy Jack Anderson", 1998; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 35)
    - Interview: "Original - Tape #2 Nancy Murphy Jack Anderson", 1998; Series 15 Subseries 2 (Box 464, Cassette 36)